## **DAWN NGUYEN**

## PRODUCT DESIGNER









Urbana, IL

anhnguyen19903@gmail.com

(714) 483 4589

http://dawnuxi.com

I love good product design and I am passionate in AR/VR technology. I design to empower people, solve human problems and create delightful experience. With a vision for innovation, I aim for great challenges. My expertise includes user and market research, developing conceptual diagrams, wireframes, visual mockups, prototypes and front-end development.

Skills	1	ools

Sketching	Branding	Design Thinking	Photoshop	Proto.io
HTML5/CSS3	Content Strategy	3D Modeling	After Effects	Invision
JQuery	Agile Development	3D Rendering	Illustrators	Framer
Prototyping	Interaction Design	Animation	Premiere	Origami
<b>Usability Testing</b>	Information Architecture	UI/UX	Sketch3	Principle
A/B testing	Video Editing	VR/AR	Paper & Markers	Unity3D
Wireframing	Critical Thinking	Swift	Dreamweaver	Cinema4D
Analytics	User Research	Java	Animate/Flash	Houdini
Personas	Motion Graphics	C#	Edge Animate	Solidworks

## Experience

**2017-Present UI/UX Design & Development Intern -** Syngenta US Champaign, IL Designing and developing user interactive interface and motion graphics Participating brainstorming, ideation and project development stage.

Conducting user experience research and designing web and mobile application

**2017-Present UI/UX & VR Intern** - National Center for Supercomputing Application Champaign, IL Designing Virtual Reality Controller and interfaces for AVL's Virtual Director software in order to improve Scientific Data Visualization Design's experience, workflows and collaboration with scientists

Designed and developed Virtual Reality experience on WebVR platform to showcase dome view production

Conducted User Experience Research and User Testing

Redesigned Advanced Visualization Lab's web interface to attract and engage the general public to computational scientific research and contents better

Produced low and medium quality prototypes to test and learning user behavior Gathered and produced a demo of all the AVL's works in the past for the team to show in SIGGRAPH 2017 Conference in Los Angeles

**2017-Present Design Consultant & Front-end Developer -** Cube Consulting Champaign, IL Assisted local business in marketing, design and development for digital products

**2016-8/2017 Video Producer** - University of Illinois Housing Champaign, IL Filmed and edited commercial and event videos as well as design and animated motion graphics for advertisement and marketing's projects

**2011–2013 Front-End Web Developer** - Maarka Data Solutions Irvine, CA Designed and developed better UX/UI on the company's old website

## Education

2015–2018 University of Illinois, at Urbana–Champaign Industrial Design

2013-2015 Orange Coast College in California

Animation & Digital Media Design